okay this is the most depressing one SSL
massive receiver that dollars
this is Kuwait 1991 so ask away quite
and me know as he enters no enter you
know six-lane highway say highway
six-lane highway that sigh scurrilous
these are all Iraqi soldiers so on sold
al-asiri keys
they attacked Kuwait at a current quite
easily Kuwait has no army ok facil quite
no tiene hurts it they opened up all the
banks they got all the gold ever here on
todos van cause a current Allah lotto
they raped all the pretty women the
Aladdin at a las mujeres well yeah they
stole all the Mercedes Benzes Sarah why
don't all those cars Mercedes Benz and
they are feeling good yeah US Sen
tambien okay they got gold women and
Mercedes Benz tienen autumn mujeres a
Mercedes Benz and they are driving their
Mercedes Benz back to Iraq even manic
and oh so Marcellus vans the regressor
Iraq then I don't know you know six
armies French English American they all
join together yes a near Anka Messiah
here see tous English as Francis's style
need answers
and they have orders to bomb - bomb
these guys opinion or the next day
Bombardier I use it took like 20 minutes
I think children adore the veinte
minutos first a bomb the last
mercedes-benz primero Bombardier on el
último mercedes-benz let they bomb the
first Mercedes we are go for murder on
el primer merciless winds so nobody can
go forward nobody can go back a second
Aleppo a rainy parallel Antony para trás
and then slowly they bomb all the others
Lent Amenti Bombardier on a los demás
and they killed everybody in Matera
Nepal 2,000 people in about 20 minutes
creo que como dos mil personas and
Bentham in notice why I have this
picture poor captain must imagine these
guys are happy
ok your system felices they just had sex
take cars for gold and they have a new
Mercedes Benz to Iran relaciones
sexuales su carro star a plateau de Oro
a 1000 meter series vents two minutes
later
dos minutos s place they are wrapped in
fire it's done name well it doesn't fail
you know true story
historia berry Rica why I put this
picture there for kept possessed imagine
ie yeah how long does it take to go to
hell is it suna Campo del tiempo Qataris
and llegar al in fear you know if I trip
on this last step on the white thing you
know see me crack my head open
see Metro Pearson and Ultimo's calendar
step a CEO Blanco ma abre la cabeza how
long does it take to go to hell cuanto
tiempo today and llegar al in fear no I
mean minimum about 10 seconds 15 seconds
me more the asking the second dose
maximum 49 days Maximo quarantine the
radius that's your window it says 11th
and I sell Rango y por que you don't
have to go anywhere okay no tienes que
de ninguna lado when I walk out the door
cuando kamini Sarika por la puerta it's
not that I walk towards the door I see
penny I say hi penny and then I walk out
hi Carmen I then I walk out the door
no it's kamini hace la puerta where
penny letting all a penny Lagos algo
para that's not how reality works no
it's a C comma functional r le dad and
it's very it's amazing but it's true yes
sir presented pero es verdad my mind
makes a picture of a medium-sized or me
mente hace una imagen de una Puerta de
manyu Mariano then I walk two steps
Rhaego coming of those pesos then my
mind makes a picture of a slightly
bigger door level momenta Sehun imagined
in a porta mas grande then I walk two
more steps Rio Camino Dos Passos mass
the steps are also coming from my mind
but I don't want to talk about it means
pesos Damian in the momento para no
quiero ver a circle a story then my mind
makes a big a big a big hole Rev ami
mente as you know your Ma's Grande
and the world is coming from your mind
at sixty-five frames per second el mundo
viene that to maintain a Santa Cinco
samia's poor Segundo Santa Cinco Quadros
poor Segundo the the teaching from the
gardener that I didn't teach this time
Lance any answer the nagarjuna can no
ensign Estevez on one map a drum a path
first line merrily Nia nobody goes
anywhere
Nadia Savannah moon lado nobody comes
from anywhere Nadia be ended an Engel
lado your mind makes bigger door
pictures to mental support as a
mechanism part as much grandes then your
mind makes smaller door pictures got to
mentor as a mechanism part as mass spec
Kenya's and you call it walking through
the door ito Lamas caminar por la puerta
okay
65 projections for per second senpai
Cinco projections poor Segundo so how
long does it take to go to hell Asik a
quantity empanadas in general in fear no
faster than a Kuwaiti Mercedes must fast
he'll kill mercilessly kawaii okay to go
from happy life they either a bit of a
lease to wrapped in fire star am welcome
file okay it's it's faster than that
it's my rapid okay so okay don't think
I'm just making a story okay
Enoch Lancaster invent and on a story as
a hundred percent true let's see em
portion Tyrell if we really understood
the situation we would all be like you
know Lady of Guadalupe or something real
maintained and Aramis esto sería most
como la virgin de Guadalupe we would all
be very very careful you know Celia most
extreme element equity losses okay
anyway if I tell you 100 times maybe I
will understand also care for Mozilla
CCC loss yokomo CMS's kisses Joe Silva
Olympian okay
[Music]
okay here's a famous line that I
remember from my teacher
I guess tell Alina from Osaka you're
required of them in maestro lunch a
language in Turkey Park in the mid
sanguine Sun news sipping i'm cho
cheated my cooper schockner rigged up a
little topic you're in our past life we
have been a pig many times in history de
pasar hemos sido sir those muchas veces
in America we don't have many we don't
have any pigs walking around the city in
America in a thousand years not tenemos
mucho Spartacus coming I'm not ready
Lord LSU that so you can't really
appreciate what a wild feral pig in a
city looks like a ck realmente no puedo
creer como se va parka Salvaje por la
ciudad but when you go to India pero
cuando la mia is unbelievable I think
really that's trash everywhere every few
feet there's trash poopoo people poo poo
pee pee sixty percent of Indians still
poo poo and pee pee on the street
Eva Suvarov por todos lados a kilometer
a basura Sesenta por ciento like Antonia
say Popeye PPF where then walking down
the street is like playing a game you
know you're jumping a cabin that poor
guy is come with jugando buzz rincon de
la la la la then the pigs are walking up
and down the street eating all the way
he lost where does one come in enough
for estella can you come you know satola
and it's chaos and it the smell is
unbelievable yes some cows yellow
lorries gravely and the llama stand here
your past lives as those pigs yellamma
is a key to win a Posada como esto
service if you take all the poop of the
day the circus total pop pocket communal
that power will be higher than Mount
Everest
si si Montaigne cerium a Celtic ailment
everest the purple you have personally l
pop orchid to personalmente s Camino the
people you have drunk as a as a pig in
your past lives l PP Cass tomorrow
como
ser Dontos villas Posadas is bigger than
like Chalobah is más grande que la voce
lappa okay don't forget que no se la
salle vida